(Penny:)Oh, I think I see our next stop.
(Sheldon:)You can't be serious.
It I wanted to waste my time
on nonsense,
(Sheldon:)I'd follow Leonard on Instagram.
(Penny:)No, come on.
Tonight, we are trying new things.
Oh! That's a lot of incense.
(Sheldon:)Or someone set a hippie on fire.
(Bernadette(on phone):)Yeah, honey,
I'm still stuck at work.
(Howard:)Really?
Penny said that?
(Bernadette(on phone):)Okay, it's true.
I'm sorry.
(Bernadette(on phone):)I'll see you at home.
(Bernadette(on phone):)Yeah, yeah, I'll put it on.
(Leonard:)You and I never just
hang out like this. Why is that?
(Amy:)-I know. it's weird, right?
-Yeah. We should do it more often.
(Amy:)Oh, no. I mean,
this is weird right now.
(Leonard:)-It's Penny.
-ls she still mad?